>> Jem Young: 好的，让我们改变我们的家庭目录
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: All right, so let's change
our home directory, which we did so
那是 cd 字号
that's cd tilde.
>> Jem Young: 老实说，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And honestly,
我之前不知道我是个成年人，那个乌贼的符号叫做波浪符。
I didn't know until I think I was an adult
that the squiggle sign is called a tilde.
然后另一个呢他叫什么
And then the other one,
the what he called it?
在波浪线上的那个也被称为坟墓标志我也不知道
The same one that's on the tilde is called
a grave marker that I didn't know either.
我知道当你满满的时候你会学到很多东西
Yeah, I know you learn all sorts of
stuff when your run a full stack.
我们想做一个 .ssh 目录
What we wanna do is we wanna
make a .ssh directory,
因为缺省情况下， SSH 密钥在 .ssh 目录中。
because our SSH keys are by
default in the .ssh directory.
我们现在想以这个用户身份登录
We wanna be able to
login as this user now,
因为我们会在第二次禁用 root 用户登录。
because we're gonna disable
root login in a second.
因此， mkdir -p， -p 仅创建一个目录 ( 如果该目录尚不存在) 。
So mkdir -p, the -p just creates
a directory if it doesn't already exist.
然后是 ~ /.ssh ，所以我们正在创建一个 .ssh 目录。
And then ~/.ssh, so
we're creating a .ssh directory.
我会在这里做的 mkdir -p ~/.ssh
I'm gonna do that here, mkdir -p ~/.ssh.
我们做了一个 ls -a
And we do an ls -a, yeah,
它会列出我们所有的目录
it'll list out all of our directories.
其实我想我要我不要我要 -a
Actually, I think I want -l, no I want -a.
缺省情况下，前面有点的任何内容都被视为隐藏目录。
Anything with a dot in front of it is
considered a hidden directory by default.
如果我不做任何事情，因为我没有目录。
If I do ls nothing shows up,
because I have no directories.
但是当我执行 ls -a 时，会看到所有隐藏目录或
But when I do an ls -a will see
all the hidden directories or
隐藏的文件。
hidden files that are in here.
>> Jem Young: 在那里。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Right there.
现在，我们将创建一个新的文件，我们将使用 vim。
So now, we're gonna create a new file,
we're gonna use vim.
我们要创建一个叫授权钥匙的文件
We're gonna create a file
called authorized keys, and
我们会把我们的公钥贴在我们的授权钥匙文件里
when we do that we're gonna paste our
public key into our authorized key file.
同样地，我们所做的，数字海洋是如何设置你的服务器的。
Again exactly what we did,
how digital ocean sets up your server.
当您创建根目录时，它会为您执行此操作，但是
It does this for
you when you create a root directory, but
现在我们为新用户做这个
now we're just doing this for
our new user.
所以我们可以 SSH
So we can SSH in, so
vi ~/.ssh/authorized_keys。
vi ~/.ssh/authorized_keys.
我现在就去做希望我能给你授权
I'm going to do that now,
hopefully I can spell authorized right,
我是个可怕的蜘蛛
I'm a terrible speller.
.ssh/authorized_keys。
.ssh/authorized_keys.
从那里，我将从我的另一个终端那里抓取我的公钥，
And from there, I am going to grab my
public key from my other terminal, so
我只是想把它烧起来
I'm just gonna
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I'm just gonna fire.
我只是打开了另一个终端什么都没有
I just opened up another terminal,
nothing fancy.
其实以前复制过但我要把 CD 放入我的点安全目录里
Actually copied that before but I'm
going to CD into my dot safe directory.
然后我要去做我做的猫，所以 fsfe2。
And then I'm going to cat that I made,
so fsfe2.
记住它是 pub pub ，我就是要复制这个。
Remember it's the dot pub, and
I'm just going to copy this.
但我要插入其中我要把它贴在这
But I'm just gonna insert,
I'm gonna paste that in.
> > Jem Young: 然后我去拯救它
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And then I'm gonna save it.
> > Jem Young: 到目前为止所有人都在吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Everybody with me so far?
所以你创建一个授权的密钥文件，
So you create an authorized key file,
然后将它粘贴到要 SSH 的公用密钥中。
and then you paste it in your
public key that you wanna SSH into.
所以 vi，我们打开它来编辑，如果你和 vi 打开它的文件不存在，
So vi, we open it to edit, and if a file
doesn't exist when you open it with vi,
它会在你写的时候给你创造，然后就写辞职了，或者对。
it'll create it for you when you write it,
and then just write quit, or yeah.
我不喜欢写 quit ，因为它听起来好像是右键单击，但是
I don't like saying write quit, because
it sounds like saying right click, but
我要把 WQ和 UWQ 说出来
I'll say WQ, UWQ out of it.
>> Jem Young: 对。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Right.
> > Jem Young: 大家都好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Everybody good so far?
好的。 好吧现在
Okay.
All right, so now,
我们要做的是退出然后我们就退出
what we're gonna do is we're gonna exit,
and then we're gonna exit.
所以离开一次让我们重新扎根
So exiting one time
puts us back in a root,
当我们切换用户时，我们打开了一个新的外壳。
cuz all we did when we switched users,
we opened a new shell.
所以我们要离开那里再次退出然后我们就去
So we're gonna exit out of there,
exit again, then we're gonna ssh in
我们的新用户名 >> Jem Young:
with our new user name
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So exits,
然后退出然后
then exits, and then
>> Jem Young: Gonna ssh 与用户名 Jem
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Gonna ssh with user name Jem
在 IP 地址处。
at the IP address.
>> Jem Young: 如果我贴的东西是对的，我就在我的服务器里
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
if I pasted things right, I'm in my server